

# Sen Lu

H

24 November 1999



United Kingdom 07749784898



https://sen6666666.github.io/



sen.lu@postgrad.manchester.ac.uk

## About me —

As an ambitious student specializing in robotics, I am deeply committed to academic excellence. With a diverse set of skills, technical competencies and innovative perspectives, I am prepared to combine my efforts with the strategic vision of the organisation in order to make significant advances in the field of robotics.

# Skills -

Ansys

Python(ROS2)

Arduino

SolidWorks

MaLab

(\*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

#### Education

2019-2023 Bachelor of Engineering, University of Sussex

Majoring in Mechanical Engineering with Robotics

2023-2024 Master of Science, University of Manchester Manchester, UK

Brighton,UK

Majoring in Robotics

#### (Awards)

2022 Won first prize in an industrial design competition at the University of

Sussex

2023 Received the Best Project Award from the Institution of Engineers, UK

### Experience

July 2020-August 2020:

 $Company: China, Qingdao, Qingdao\ Wangshengyuan\ Metals\ Technology\ Co.$ 

Job title:CAD Design and Drawing

Detail:1.Machining shop operator

2.Used Solidwork to finish high-quality project drawings.

Jun 2022-Aug 2022

Company: China, Shanghai, SF Express

Job title:Intelligent logistics system assistant

Detail: 1. Optimize the robot's trajectory and actions through Python programming

2. Participated in the training of express station employees. Taught them how to operate

the robot properly

### Personal Project

1.Gloves designed to help stroke victims recover

Connect the glove to the camera. When a normal person makes an action in front of the camera, the glove will follow the corresponding action. In addition, each finger of the glove also corresponds to a different function, such as turning on the TV, calling the doctor, drinking water, etc., which can encourage patients to move their fingers.

2.Leo Rover

Assemble the Leo Rover robot with my team members and develop related functions (Machine Vision)